

# CONTACT

stephaniecinelli@gmail.com

+46 738934084

Stockholm - Sweden

www.linkedin.com/in/ stephanie-cinelli-ruzzi

github.com/stecinelli

### **SKILLS**

- React (Redux) & React Native
- HTML / CSS / SASS
- NodeJS
- ExpressJS
- GraphQL
- MongoDB / PostgreSQL
- Docker
- AWS

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

Agile Pratices & Culture
Telefonica (2019) | FIAP (2021)

**User Experience** FIAP (2021)

DevOps FIAP (2021)

## **AWARDS**

Value Person 2019, 2018, 2017 | Vivo

Program Genesys Premiation 2016 | Vivo

# **LANGUAGES**

Portuguese – Native English – Fluent Spanish – Proficient Swedish – Basic

# **Stephanie Cinelli**

Full Stack Developer

React.js | Node.js | TypeScript | Agile

#### **PROFILE**

Software Developer passionate for learning and solving complex problems and certificated on Agile, CX, UX and DevOps. I've worked for 7 years in software development projects focused on Customer Experience, and was awarded for 4 consecutive years for being a collaborative, innovative and reliable professional.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Full Stack Developer Consultant**

Salt - Sweden | Dec. 2022 - Present

- Created different apps as e-commerce, timer, trivia and SPAs using TypeScript and deployed them to AWS and Netlify.
- Contribution on mobile apps projects using React Native.

#### **Digital Transformation Consultant**

Vivo - Telefonica Brazil | May. 2021 - Oct. 2021

- Change agent acting to Vivo's Digital Transformation, focused on digitalization
  of the customer care.
- Creating and aligning the features between APP and Website to improve the CX and the UX.
- · Assuring through indicators the digital engagement improvement.

#### **Project Team Lead**

Vivo - Telefonica Brazil | May. 2018 - Apr. 2021

- Coordination of a Project Analysts team, focused in the intermediation of the IT team and UX team.
- Responsible for the implementation of Agile methodologies, definition of a effective team structure and maintain the motivation.

#### Sr. Project Analyst

Vivo - Telefonica Brazil | May. 2017 - Apr. 2018

- Project management focused on UX, using Artificial Intelligence to create service channels on social media (Whatsapp and Facebook).
- Operational projects focused on restructuring the customer relationship model, including the implementation of Vivo DNA.

# **EDUCATION**

#### Bootcamp, Full Stack JavaScript

SALT| Set. 2022 - Nov. 2022

#### **GBA**, Leadership and People Management

Conquer School | Jul. 2019 - Dec. 2019

#### **MBA, Consumer Experience**

ESPM | Jan. 2014 - Dec. 2015

#### **BBA, Business Administration and Management**

FGV | Jan. 2009 - Dec. 2012